(Sheldon:)Please, please, please.
Let me meet Hawking.
- l told you no.
- But I said I'm sorry.
(Howard:)No, you said,
"Would it help if I said'I'm sorry'?"
Well, and you never answered me.
(Sheldon:)So who owes whom an apology now?
(Howard:)Sheldon, you're a condescending jerk.
(Howard:)Why on earth would I want
to do something nice for you?
(Sheldon:)To go to Jewish heaven?
(Howard:)Jews don't have heaven.
Well, then, to avoid Jewish hell?
(Howard:)Have you met my mother?
I live in Jewish hell.
(Sheldon:)Howard, please.
This is Stephen Hawking.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps my only intellectual equal.
(Howard:)You can't be serious.
Try to put yourseIf in my place.
lmagine you're the sole human being...
(Sheldon:)...living on a planet
populated with nothing but dogs.
(Sheldon:)And then it turns out
there's another human being.